Guide to the Victor F. Germack and Lori Shepard Germack Collection of Photographs of Indians of North America
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Stereographs, circa 1860-circa 1925; Series III; 3; (3 boxes)
  - Keystone View Company
    - "I" Series
      Arranged sequentially by the "I" series number.
      Set of stereographs with an unidentified title produced and distributed by the Keystone View Company, circa 1922, that depict different American Indian groups.
      - Kasaan Village, Indians and Canoes, Alaska (No. I1, No. 1081, No. 21038T, and No. 21038), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 436-437)
        One card with variant title: In the Land of the Totem Poles, The Indian Village of Kasaan, Alaska.
      - Chief's House, Bear and Wolf Totems, Fort Wrangell, Alaska (No. I2 and No. 21034), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 438)
      - Stop for Lunch, Malamut Indians, Alaska (No. I3 and No. 11558), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 439)
      - Malamut Indian Fish Cache, Alaska (No. I4 and No. 21011), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 440)
      - A Group of Malamut Children Playing, Alaska (No. I5 and No. 21022), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 441)
      - An Indian Canoe, Yukon River, Alaska (No. I6 and No. 21021), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 442)
      - Puckalook Having a Time, Alaska (No. I7 and No. 6319), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 443)
      - Malemute Indians Moving Camp (No. I8 and No. 11540), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 444)
      - Indian Burial Houses, Juneau City, Alaska (No. I9 and No. 21035), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 445)
      - A Thriving Family of Snake River Indians, Alaska (No. I10 and No. 21036), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 446)
      - Snake River Indians' Scalp Dance (No. I11 and No. 21037), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 447)
      - Siwash Indians at Dinner in Tepee on the Banks of Fraser River, British Columbia, Canada (No. I12 and No. 13818), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 448)
      - Indian Girl with Travois, Calgary, Canada (No. I13 and No. 23342), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 449)
      - An Open Air Nursery, Indian Family of Prince Edward Island, Canada (No. I14 and No. 13881), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 450)
      - Splendid Group, Indian Buffalo Hunt, in Convention Hall, Jamestown Exposition (No. I15 and No. 23342), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 451)
      - Indians at Home, Atlanta Exposition, Georgia (No. I16 and No. 23341), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 452)
      - Geronimo, the Famous Apache Chief, Skinning the Buffalo After the Hunt. Oklahoma (No. I17, No. 17, and No. V23174 ), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 453-454)
      - Geronimo Shooting an Arrow, Saint Louis Exposition (No. I18 and No. 23340), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 455)
      - Home Life of Sac and Fox Indians. With Sleeping Papoose, Sac and Fox Reservation, Oklahoma (No. I19 and No. V23177), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 456)
      - Haskell Institute, Lawrence, Kansas (No. I20 and No. 23333), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 457)
      - Omaha Indians, Nebraska (No. I21 and No. 23334), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 458)
      - Making an Indian Bow, Indian Camp, World's Fair, 1904, Saint Louis, Missouri (No. I22 and No. 23339), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 459)
      - Two Guns White Calf, the Blackfeet Chief Whose Profile Is on the Buffalo Nickel (No. I23 and No. 32610), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 460)
      - Chippewa Squaw and Papoose (No. I24 and No. 20959), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 461)
      - Warpi Yahdinjen, An Old Chippewa (No. I25 and No. 20958), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 462)
      - Chippewa Squaw Making Birch Canoe (No. I26 and No. 20957), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 463)
      - Chippewa Squaws Braiding Rush Mats (No. I27 and No. 20956), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 464)
      - A Winnebago Chief, Minnesota (No. I28 and No. 23335), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 465)
        Associated Materials: Stereograph card with the same image published by William H. Rau, Winnebago Indian Chief Posed Standing and Holding a Cased Photograph (No. Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1890
      - Winnebago Squaw Carrying Wood (No. I29 and No. 23336), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 466)
      - Winnebago Squaws on Horseback (No. I30 and No. 23337), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 467)
      - Chief Blackhead and Family, Winnebago Indians (No. I31 and No. W23322), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 468)
      - Group of Winnebago Braves in Full Feather (No. I32 and No. 23173), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 469)
      - An Old Sioux and Camp (No. I33, No. 33, and No. 23315), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 470-470a)
      - A Sioux Musician (No. I34 and No. 23319), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 471-472)
      - Family Group of Sioux and Lodge (No. I35 and No. 23320), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 473-474)
      - Mounted Sioux and Camp (No. I36 and No. 23318), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 475-476)
      - Sioux Indian Riders Before Horse Race (No. I37 and No. 23317), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 477)
      - Group of Sioux Indians Watching a Horse Race (No. I38 and No. 23321), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 478)
      - Indian Boys Race at Standing Rock, North Dakota (No. I39 and No. 23346), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 479)
      - Katen Yance, An Old Sioux Warrior (No. I40 and No. 23316), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 480-481)
      - The Old Bucks in Council (No. I41 and No. 23347), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 482-483)
      - Feathered and Painted Braves of the Warlike Sioux Indians, Nebraska (No. I42 and No. V23176), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 484)
      - Passing Peace Pipe Around Council (No. I43 and No. 23345), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 485-486)
      - Blackfeet Indians Preparing for Medicine Lodge Ceremony, Glacier National Park, Montana (No. I44, No. 188, and No. 23000), circa 1922; (3 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 487-489)
      - Blackfeet Indians Ready to Enter Medicine Lodge, Two Medicine Country, Glacier National Park (No. I45 and No. 23002), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 490)
      - Procession of Squaws, Blackfeet Medicine Lodge Glacier National Park, Montana (No. I46 and No. 23001), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 491)
      - Powwow in the Medicine Lodge, Blackfeet Indians of Glacier National Park (No. I47 and No. 23003), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 492)
      - Scene at a Feast Dance on the Crow Reservation, Near Billings, Montana, Watching the Dance (No. I48 and No. V23175), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 493)
      - Mounted Indians Gaffing Salmon in the Winachee River, Washington (No. I49 and No. 23329), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 494)
      - Statue of Sacajawea Showing Way to Lewis and Clark City Park, Portland, Oregon (No. I50 and No. 14238), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 495)
      - Digger Indian, California (No. I51 and No. 23331), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 496)
      - Splendid Type of Hopi Indian, Hopi Pueblo, Arizona (No. I52 and No. 23129), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 497)
      - Hopi Chief 128 Years Old (No. I53 and No. 23327), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 498)
      - Picturesque Wolpi (North) 600 Feet Above Desert, Hopi Indian Reservation, Arizona (No. I54 and No. V23323), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 499)
      - Hopi Indians and their Strange Homes Beside the Dance Rock, Wolpi, Arizona (No. I55 and No. V23195), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 500)
      - The Dance Rock of the Hopis, revered by the Indians, Wolpi, Arizona (No. I56 and No. V23196), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 501)
      - Government Well, Sole Water Supply for Indian Village of Oraibi, Arizona (No. I57 and No. V23184), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 502)
      - Indian Girls Weaving Baskets, Village of Shipaulovi, Hopi Reservation, Arizona (No. I58 and No. V23186), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 503)
      - Home Duties of the Hopi Man, a Scene at the Indian Village of Oraibi, Arizona (No. I59 and No. V23187), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 504-505)
      - Primitive Methods, a Hopi Squaw Coiling Clay into Pottery, Oraibi, Arizona (No. I60 and No. V23189), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 506)
      - Primitive Artists, Indian Women Decorating Pottery, Hopi Reservation, Arizona (No. I61, No. 61, and No. V23190), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 507-508)
      - Terrace Homes of Hopi Indians, Street Scene in Oraibi, Hopi Reservation, Arizona (No. I62 and No. V23199), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 509-510)
      - A Morning Promenade, Oraibi, Hopi Reservation, Arizona (No. I63 and No. V23197), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 511)
      - The Masked Kachinas (Northern Hopi Indian Rainmakers), Village of Shonghopavi, Arizona (No. I64 and No. V23193), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 512)
      - Typical Hopi Indian Home, Mishongnovi, Arizona (No. I65 and No. V23192), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 513)
      - The Hopi House, Miniature Indian Pueblo Near El Tovar, Arizona (No. I66 and No. 23326), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 514)
      - Inside the Hopi Indian House, Artistic Handiwork of Natives, Grand Canyon, Arizona (No. I67 and No. V23200), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 515)
      - Hopi Corn Festival (No. I68 and No. 23325), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 516-517)
      - A Hopi Group Including Rain Maker and Chief, World's Fair, Saint Louis, Missouri (No. I69 and No. 23338), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 518)
      - Indian Pictographs, Arizona (No. I70 and No. V23203), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 519)
      - Navajo Silversmiths (No. I71 and No. 23324), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 520)
      - Navajo Blanket Weaving, an Indian Hogan (Hut), on the Navajo Reservation, Arizona (No. I72, No. 72, and No. V23203), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 521-522)
      - Southwest Indians, A Navajo Woman Weaving a Rug (No. I73, No. 22 and No. 23344), circa 1922; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 523-524)
      - Navajo Indian Mother and Children, Albuquerque New Mexico (No. I74, No. 74, and No. 23116), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 525-526)
      - Navajo Indian with his Flock of Sheep in Northeastern Arizona (No. I75 and No. V23182), circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 527)
    - Unidentified Series
      - Southwest Indians, Zuni Indians (No. 2 and No. 17682), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 528)
      - Indian Talking to a Cowboy in Sign Language (No. 10 and No. V23247), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 529)
      - A Skirmish between Indians and Whites, A Historic Pageant in Oklahoma (No. 11 and No. V33452), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 530)
      - A Group of Indians on the Side Line, Between Sham Battles of a Western Pageant, Montana (No. 36 and No. 33474), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 531)
      - Mounted Sioux Indians in Full Feather Leaving Camp, Nebraska (No. 182 and No. 16718), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 532)
      - Ute Indian and Family, Colorado (No. 204 and No. 8082), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 533)
      - As in Ancient Days, Pueblo of the Taos (No. 211 and No. 13720), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 534)
      - In the Village of Blackfeet Indians near Saint Mary's Lake, Glacier National Park, Montana (No. 342, No. 1101, No. V23181, and No. V23181T), circa 1920-1925; (3 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 535-537)
      - Eskimo Girls and Part of Crew S.S. Eric at Upernavik, Northernmost Danish Trading Post, Greenland (No. 343 and No. 13329), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 538)
      - A Navajo Rug Weaver, Indian Woman and Children, New Mexico (No. 1133 and No. 32802), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 539)
      - As in the Ancient Days, Pueblo of the Taos Indians, Taos, New Mexico (No. 1134 and No. 13720), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 540)
      - Dismantled Towers and Turrets Broken, Cliff Palace in the Mesa Verde, Colorado (No. 1135 and No. V8014 T), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 541)
      - An Eskimo Family at Fort Magnesia, Cabe Sabin, Ellsmere Land (No. 1181 and No. V13334T), circa 1920-1925; (2 stereographs) (Box 5, Folder 542-543)
      - A Hopi Indian Home in Arizona (No. P24 and No. V23192), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 544)
      - Indian Boy and Baby, Toluca, Mexico (No. P179 and No. 23619), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 545)
      - Eskimo Dog Team and Sledge, World's Fair, Saint Louis (No. P199 and No. P-15447), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 546)
      - Eskimo Boats and Native Paddlers (No. P203 and No. P-13330), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 547)
      - Summer Tents of Eskimos, Greenland (No. P274 and No. P-V27203), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 548)
      - Chief Two Guns White Calf and Companions in Medicine Lodge Ceremony, Glacier National Park, Montana (No. T164 and No. V32589T), circa 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 549)
  - Kilburn, Benjamin W.
    - Indians and Canoes, Bar Harbor, Mount Desert, Maine (No. 272), Unidentified Series, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 550)
    - Bar Harbor and Yachts, Mount Desert, Maine (No. 273 and No. 20384), Unidentified Series, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 551-552)
      One stereograph card published by the Kilburn Brothers.
    - Sceneries of Columbia River, Indians Drying Salmon, Celilo Falls, Oregon (No. 10541), Unidentified Series, circa 1896 (Box 6, Folder 553)
    - Indian Burial Place on Memaloose Island, Washington (No. 10561), Unidentified Series, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 554)
  - Luke & Wheeler
    - Noble Red Man (No. 95), Unidentified Series; Studio Portrait of Five American Indian Men, 1879-1881 (Box 6, Folder 555)
  - Martin, James Edgar
    - Kay-Ka-Ke-Oonco (Sparrow Hawk), Chippewa Warrior (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1865-1869 (Box 6, Folder 556)
      Original photograph probably by Benjamin F. Upton or Joel Emmons Whitney.
  - McLeish, William
    - White Spider, Big Thunder, or John Wakeman (Unk-Yo-Ma-Skah or Wakinyan-Tanka), Brother of Little Crow (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1871 (Box 6, Folder 557)
  - Metropolitan Syndicate Press
    - Indian Chiefs, Quanah Parker, Geronimo, Buckskin Charlie, American Horse, Little Plume, Hollow Horn in the Inaugural Parade (No.557), Metropolitan Series, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 558)
      The stereograph has halftone prints on it.
  - Morrow, Stanley J.
    - Little Six or Little Shakopee (Eatoka, Shakpedan, or Zhaagobens), Mdewakanton Indian Man, Executed at Fort Snelling, Minnesota, November 11, 1865, Unidentified Series, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 559)
      Original photograph by Joel Emmons Whitney, 1864.
    - Yanktonia Sioux as Good Scouts (No. 13), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 560)
    - First and Second Chiefs of the Mandans (Red Crow and He Who Follows the Eagle), at Fort Berthold, Dakota Territory (No. 15), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 561-562)
    - Fort Benton, Montana Territory (No. 73), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West; Street with Buildings, and Signs for Overland Hotel and Carroll Steell, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 563)
    - Medicine Bear, Medicine Bear Track, or Mysterious Grizzly Bear (Mato Wakan, Ma-To-Ican, Ma-To-O-A-Wa-Kan, Ma-To-Wuh-Kan) (No. 101), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 564)
    - Medicine Bear, Medicine Bear Track, or Mysterious Grizzly Bear (Mato Wakan, Ma-To-Ican, Ma-To-O-A-Wa-Kan, Ma-To-Wuh-Kan) (No. 102), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 565)
    - A Scaffold Burial with Bison Skulls on an Elevated Coffin (No. 109), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 566)
    - Cheyenne Warrior. Sioux Nation (No. 112), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 567)
    - Group of European Americans and American Indians at a White Wooden Building (No. 115), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 568)
    - Arikara Village at Fort Berthold, Dakota Territory (No. 122), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 569)
    - Two Kettle Warriors, Sioux Nation (No. 141), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 570)
    - Une-Pa-Che-Na Warriors, Sioux Nation (No. 145), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West; Identified as Energy Searcher and Lean Man, Gros Ventres Indians, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 571)
    - Blackfoot Warriors, Sioux Nation (No. 147), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 572)
    - Group of Eleven American Indian Men and Two European American Men by a Wooden Building (No. 147), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West; a European American Woman and Child Behind the Group, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 573)
    - Pretty Horses, Daughter of White Bull, Chief of the Sans Arc (No. 152), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 574)
    - Major Howard Bingham and White Bull, Chief of Sans Arcs Sioux, and his Family (No. 154), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 575)
    - Indian Village near Mouth of Yellowstone, also known as Yanktonite (Sioux) Tepees. Fort Rice, Dakota Territory (No. Number), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 576)
    - Pretty Sea Shells, Daughter of White Bull, Chief of the Sans Arc (No Number), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 577)
    - Group of Nine American Indian Men and a European American Man by a Log and Sod Building (No Number), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 578)
    - Ponca Indian Man (No Number), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 579)
    - Wooden Platforms and Structures (No Number), Photographic Gems from the Great North-West; Possibly a Gros Ventres Indian Village, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 580)
    - First and Second Chiefs of the Gros Ventres, Fort Berthold, Dakota (No. 27), Photographic Gems Among the Wild Indians of Dakota, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 581)
    - Group of Santee Indian Girls Wearing Blankets with European American Woman at the Nebraska Santee Mission (No Number), Photographic Gems Among the Wild Indians of Dakota, circa 1879 (Box 6, Folder 582)
  - Muybridge, Eadweard James
    - The Peace Commission Tent and Stone on which Gen. Canby was sitting when shot by Capt. Jack (No. 1601), The Modoc War, 1873 (Box 6, Folder 583)
      Published by Bradley & Rulofson, San Francisco, California.
    - A Modoc Brave on the Warpath (No. 1626), The Modoc War, 1873 (Box 6, Folder 584)
  - New Educational Series
    - Group Siouxs (No. 103), American and Foreign Views; Low Dog and Other Dakota Indians, circa 1880 (Box 6, Folder 585)
  - Nims, Franklin A.
    - Indian Boys (No. 242), The Pueblo Indians, Views of Rocky Mountain Scenery, New Mexico Series, circa 1890 (Box 6, Folder 586)
  - Nowack, Peter J.
    - Copy photograph of a lithograph print, Execution of the Thirty-Eight Sioux Indians at Mankato, Minnesota, December 26, 1862 (Milwaukee, Wisconsin: Milwaukee Lithograph & Engraving Company, 1883) (No Number), 1889 (Box 6, Folder 587)
  - O'Sullivan, Timothy H.
    - Mohave Indian Guides Caught Napping on Colorado River Beach (No Number), Unidentified Series, 1871 (Box 6, Folder 588)
    - The Start from Camp Mohave, Arizona, September 15th, 1871 (No. 1), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1871 (Box 6, Folder 589)
    - Types of Mohave Indians (No. 5), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1871 (Box 6, Folder 590)
    - Mountain Transportation (No. 7), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1871 (Box 6, Folder 591)
    - Indian Pueblo of Zuni, New Mexico; View from the Interior (No. 16), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 592)
    - Zuni Indian Girl, with Water Olla (No. 17), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 593-594)
    - Group of Zuni Indian Braves, at Their Pueblo, New Mexico (No. 19), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 595-596)
    - War Chief of the Zuni Indians (No. 20), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 597-598)
    - Aboriginal Life Among the Navajo Indians, Cañon de Chelle, New Mexico (No. 26), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 599)
    - Navajo Indian Squaw, and Child, at Their Home, in Cañon de Chelle, New Mexico (No. 27), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 600)
    - Navajo Boys and Squaw, in Front of the Quarters at Old Fort Defiance, New Mexico, Now Unoccupied by Troops (No. 28), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 601)
    - Navajo Brave and his Mother (No. 29), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 602)
    - Coyotero Apache Scouts, at Apache Lake, Sierra Blanca Mountains, Arizona (No. 31), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 603)
    - Apache Indians, as They Appear Ready for the War-Path (No. 33), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 604)
    - Alcade of the Zuni Pueblo, New Mexico (No. 46), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1873 (Box 6, Folder 605)
    - One of the Group of Pagosa Hot Springs, Showing Incrustation on the Surface (No. 38), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1874 (Box 6, Folder 606)
    - Pah-Ge, Ute Squaw, of the Kah-Poh-Teh Band, Northern New Mexico (No. 39), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1874 (Box 6, Folder 607)
    - Ute Braves, of the Kah-Poh-Teh Band, Northern New Mexico, in Full Dress (No. 40), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1874 (Box 6, Folder 608)
    - Jicarilla Apache Brave and Squaw, Lately Wedded, Abiquiu Agency, New Mexico (No. 41), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1874 (Box 6, Folder 609)
    - Shee-Zah-Nan-Tan, Jicarilla Apache Brave in Characteristic Costume, Northern New Mexico (No. 42), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 1874 (Box 6, Folder 610)
    - Characteristic Ruin, of the Pueblo San Juan, New Mexico, on the North Bank of the San Juan River, About 15 Miles West of the Mouth of Cañon Largo (No. 43), Geographical Explorations and Surveys West of 100th Meridian, Expedition of 187, 1874 (Box 6, Folder 611)
  - Payne, Henry T.
    - Cornstalk Indian Hut (No. 145), Southern California Scenery, circa 1875 (Box 6, Folder 612)
  - Rau, William H.
    - Winnebago Indian Chief Posed Standing and Holding a Cased Photograph (No. Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1890 (Box 6, Folder 613)
      Associated Materials: Stereograph card with the same image published by Keystone View Company, A Winnebago Chief, Minnesota (No. I28 and No. 23335), "I" Series.
  - Reed & McKenney
    Reed & McKenney was a partnership in Central City and Denver, Colorado
    - Studio Portrait of Six American Indian Men, Two Men Holding Rifles (No Number), Unidentified Series, circa 1862-1870 (Box 6, Folder 614)
  - Reilly, John James
    - Yo Semite Digger Indian, Yo Semite Valley, California (No. 469), Photographic Views of American Scenery, circa 1875 (Box 6, Folder 615)
    - Indian Squaws, Yo Semite Valley, California (No Number), Photographic Views of American Scenery, circa 1875 (Box 6, Folder 616)
  - Rinehart, Frank Albert
    Original photographs attributed to E. L. Clement, circa 1885-1900.
    - Presentation Dance (No Number), Unidentified Series; Native American Indian Men Participating in a Dance in the Indian Territory (Oklahoma), 1900 (Box 6, Folder 617)